I'm reading that I'm convicted and I have to
Estoy leyendo que estoy condenado y
pay costs, they're lying, I mean, they just
tengo que pagar costas mienten o sea
convicted Joan Plana, what
acaban de condenar a Joan plana que lo
happens is that Tania
que pasa es que Tania pues se le ha
forgot to do it
olvidado hacer
live, but we're waiting for her to do it,
directo pero estamos esperando que lo
this is already
haga esto ya es
final Javi Let them suffer, man, I
firme Javi Déjalos que sufran hombre yo
let them suffer Yes, yes, but of course,
los dejo que sufran Sí sí pero claro ya
when they start writing to Iker,
cuando se ponen a escribirle a Iker a
writing to four and these things, man,
escribirle a cuatro y estas cosas hombre
well, I see it a little, no, but well, I
pues lo veo un poco no pero bueno Me
imagine it will be for life
imagino que será de por vida
and context, okay, I'm not going to explain
e contexo vale no os voy a explicar otra
the full sentence to you again because I already
vez la sentencia completa porque ya lo
did it yesterday on the Salsería Channel.
hice ayer en el Canal de la salsería
Okay, now I'm also going to show you some
Vale ahora también os voy a poner algún
clips of Pablo. But Joan Planas just
clip de Pablo Pero yan planas acaba de
lost another trial or another conviction, al
perder otro juicio o otra condena al
costa, okay, final in the Supreme Court, okay, you
costa vale en firme en el supremo vale
can be the one who is
podéis ser el que es
lying, that it is a lie and that and that, that is,
mentira que es mentira y que y que o sea
and that the case is going to be taken to the
y que el caso se va a llevar al
Constitutional Court, yes, Joan, the
tribunal constitucional sí Joan lo la
UN is going to take it, the UN in the case that
ONU lo va a llevar la ONU el caso de que
you have insulted a youtuber and the
tú hayas insultado a un youtuber y el
youtuber answers you,
youtuber te conteste
eh, it's going to It's going to The UN is going to review it and
eh lo va Lo va Lo va a revisar la ONU y
then The Avengers then The
luego Los Vengadores luego Los
Avengers and then the Illuminati and
Vengadores y luego los illuminatis y
then they are going to take it to Star Wars the
luego se lo van a llevar a Star Wars el
case which is very important but apart from that
caso que es muy importante pero aparte
what the hell are you going to take the
qué qué [__] vas a llevar el
constitutional if they have not admitted your
constitucional si no te han admitido el
appeal to the Supreme Court, that is to say the
recurso en el supremo o sea el tribunal
Supreme Court It is not another instance as such the
supremo No es otra instancia como tal el
Supreme Court you send the appeal and
tribunal supremo tú mandas el recurso y
the appeal is admitted or they do not
el recurso te lo admiten o no te lo
admit it if they do not admit it it ends there
admiten si no te lo admiten se acaba ahí
and if they admit it then you can win
y si te lo admiten entonces puedes ganar
the appeal or lose it okay But first they
el recurso o perderlo vale Pero primero
have to admit it to him it is not that he
te lo tienen que admitir a él no es que
lost in the Supreme Court it is that they have not
haya perdido en el supremo es que no le
admitted him it is that they have not
han admitido es que no le han admitido
even admitted his appeal
ni siquiera el recurso
okay Accept it another sentence in ca as the
vale Acéptalo otra condena en ca como
same thing is going to happen to you with the
también te va a pasar lo mismo con la
nicoteca because the nicoteca case is
nicoteca porque caso de la nicoteca
also going to happen to you you have spent
también te va a pasar se habéis pegado
a few years saying that you were going to
unos cuantos de años diciendo que ibais
win and that and that and that little else and that
a ganar y que y que y que poco más y que
Pablo was a shitty lawyer well Pablo
Pablo era una [__] de abogado pues
has won Your lawyer okay That's it
Pablo le ha ganado A tu abogado vale Ya
nothing happens to you they have
está no pasa nada a ti a ti te han
sentenced you to ca I was sentenced to 0
condenado a ca a mí me condenaron a 0
eur okay Now you have a lawsuit with me
eur vale Ahora tienes un pleito conmigo
in which you go back to Now you quantify
en el que vuelves a Ahora sí cuantificas
from the beginning Now if you lose
desde el principio Ahora sí si pierdes
things go according to the 80,000 I'm not
las cosas van en función a los 80.000 no
telling you anything How is that going to explode and what you
te digo nada Cómo va a explotar eso y lo
're going to lengthen, well that one you're
que lo vas a alargar pu ese ese sí que
going to take to the to the court of
lo vas a llevar al a a a al tribunal de
the aya okay I want Tania to explain it to me
la aya vale Yo quiero que me lo explique
pm is that she hasn't even explained it Tania
Tania pm es que ni lo ha explicado Tania
pm nor has she posted it on her
pm ni lo ha fijado en su cuenta de
Twitter account The the Pilar lady is
Twitter La la Pilar la señora esta del
crazy Pilar see okay Pilar see she's
demonio la Pilar verir vale Pilar verir
going to the lady who to the people
se está yendo a la señora que a la gente
who are sharing the sentence in
que está compartiendo la la condena en
Costa Okay and she's defending it It's already
Costa Vale y lo está defendiendo Ya está
appealed it's already appealed Pilar or in other words
recurrido ya está recurrido Pilar o sea
Pilar sticks with months posted on her
Pilar se pega con meses fijado en su
profile it was the most the
perfil era lo más
most important thing in her life on social networks
su lo más importante de su vida en redes
was to post on her profile that they
era fijar en su perfil que a mí me
had convicted me in Costa with what
habían condenado en Costa con lo de
Diego Arrabal did that Diego Arrabal started
Diego arrabal que Diego arrabal se puso
saying that that is paying his
a decir que eso es pagarle a él el
lawyer paying him the solicitor and that's
abogado pagarle a él el procurador y eso
not like that or  well, the costs are the little piece
no es así o sea las costas es el trocito
of the appeal without more, that is, the costs
del recurso ese sin más o sea las costas
depend on how the procedure ends, if I
depende cóm termine el procedimiento si
win or lose, well, they are compensated with that,
gano o pierdo pues se compensan con esa
I do not have to pay. Right now, nothing is
yo no tengo que pagar Ahora mismo nada
worth it,
vale
but Pilar posted it, do you remember that she
e pero Pilar se lo fijó os acordáis que
posted it on her Twitter profile as
se lo fijó en su perfil de Twitter como
if it were the most important thing in her life?
si fuera lo más importante de su vida
Well, now this is a final sentence. It has
Bueno pues ahora esto que es una condena
already been appealed. Well, let's see, Pilar.
firme Ya está recurrido pues a ver Pilar
Explain to me. Where is the
Explícame En dónde está recurrido lo
next appeal being made to the galactic court? This is the most important thing I
próximo al tribunal galáctico es lo más
need for Star Wars to explain it to you.
necesito que lo explique la t Star Wars
It's that Tania, for whatever reason, has not
Es que la Tania por lo que sea no ha
reported anything about this sentence. But neither
puesto nada de esta sentencia Pero ni la
has Tania reported it nor have they reported
ha puesto la Tania ni le han puesto
any to her, none have reported any of them. This
ninguno ninguno ninguno ha puesto esto
is the second one. Well, I don't even know how many
es la segunda Bueno yo no sé ni Cuántos
trials the plan has lost there, but
juicios lleva perdido el plan allá pero
trials and a lot of things that she has
juicios y un montón de cosas que ha
done, okay. Well, that one has already been appealed.
hecho vale Bueno ya está recurrido ese
Pilar needs to explain to us where
Pilar le falta explicarnos dónde se
a final sentence can be appealed, okay, once she
recurre una sentencia firme vale una vez
explains it to us, Pilar, we will read you,
que nos lo explique Pilar te leeremos
okay, ridiculous lady, ridiculous lady,
vale señora ridícula señora ridícula
totally, this is her in a space the other
total esto es ella en un space el otro
day  wait the other day not last night
día espérate el otro día no anoche
look at him eh he's already messing with the haters
fijaros el eh se mete ya con los hater
of the kids look look at the lady with
de la chavalería mira mira la señora con
elp Lucas with
elp Lucas con la
Electra I really see my great-grandmother
Electra yo veo de verdad a mi bisabuela
doing this I mean I see my
haciendo esto O sea yo veo a mi
great-grandmother doing this on the
bisabuela haciendo esto en
internet No look with Wilson not with
internet No mira con el Wilson no con
those she rubs elbows with all day
los que ella se codea todo el día
illas the first whoever it is
illas el primero el que sea
eh who breaks Fran's request that they
eh que rompe la petición de Fran de que
drop the subject which is what suits him
dejen el tema que es lo que le conviene
Oh look who's the first to break
Ah que ve quién es el primero que rompe
Fran's request that they drop the subject
la petición de Fran de que dejen el tema
eh Well you tell me Pilar because I keep
eh Pues dímelo tú Pilar porque yo sigo
seeing videos being uploaded on YouTube
viendo que se suben vídeos en YouTube
about the
sobre el tema de
Fran issue and it wasn't me but of course you you
Fran y no he sido yo pero claro tú tú
What you're pointing out is if I
Aquí lo que estás señalando es si lo
upload it that I'll upload whatever I want and
subo yo que Subiré lo que me dé la gana
Fran won't care you know and I won't
y a Fran le va a dar igual sabes y yo no
and I'm not saying anything about the subject that
y yo no digo nada del tema que no
Fran wouldn't want to say you know but ah
quisiera Fran que dijera sabes pero ah
Frank has made a request that we not
que Frank ha hecho una petición que no
talk about the subject Frank has made a
se hable del tema Frank ha hecho una
request that we not speculate about the
petición que no se especule con el tema
judicial issue and that he be given  a little bit of a
judicial y que se le dé un poquito de
truce No, that's already good, no, not too much.
tregua No que ya está bien no también no
On Sunday we're going to do a podcast, eh. By
El domingo vamos a hacer podcast eh Por
the way,
cierto
eh. On Sunday we're going to do a podcast, which I don't
eh El domingo vamos a hacer
know if I'm going to be able to get.
podc lo que no sé si voy a poder
Well, we're going to do a podcast in
conseguir Bueno vamos a hacer podc en
theory because I'm writing to the
teoría porque Estoy escribiéndole a los
guests that I want and I don't know if I'm
invitados que quiero y no sé si con un
going to be able to get it in one day, but well, I've already written to
día lo voy a poder conseguir pero bueno
the one I want to come and
le he escrito ya al que quiero que venga
see if they
a ver si me
answer me, but let's say that he's pointing out that if
contesta pero vamos que está señalando
I make any content, if I
si yo hago algún contenido que si yo
make any content, if other
hago algún contenido si lo hace otra
people do it, they won't care. I'm telling you, it's
gente le va dar igual ya te lo digo está
in a country that
en un país ya lo rompió
Javi already broke it today, you made a meme today you made a meme
Javi hoy hiz un meme hoy hiz un meme
throwing at Cristina again. Oh, I
tirándole a Cristina otra vez Ah que yo
broke Fran's request because I
he roto la petición de de Fran porque
made a meme throwing at Cristina. Look, I
hice un meme tirandole a Cristina Mirad
mean, look at what they consider that
o sea Mirad lo que consideran ellos que
I broke Fran's request, eh.
yo he roto la petición de Fran eh
Look at this, this
Mirad esto este
t, they're going to explode with hatred totally,
t van a reventar de odio totalmente de
AIO, and
aio y
frustration, that right away, as soon as
frustración eso enseguida apenas terminó
the live ended, well, well, we'll see how long
el directo bueno bueno pues ya veremos
Fran's request lasts, he's in
lo que dura la petición de Fran está en
a very complicated country with very
un país muy complicado con leyes muy
complicated laws and very  severe and let's see if
complicadas y muy severas y a ver que si
Pilar you know where he is you know where
Pilar sabes dónde está sabes dónde está
Fran is in
Fran en
Thailand okay near Bangkok
Tailandia vale cerca de Bangkok
the New York of China You remember not the
la Nueva York de China Te acuerdas no la
New York of China and they are
Nueva York de China y son amigos de
real friends and they leave this matter and let it be
verdad y dejan este asunto y que se
resolved as best as possible Ah okay okay And thank you
resuelva lo mejor posible Ah vale vale Y
very much
muchas gracias
elestra in no time Pilar Ah okay let's
elestra en nada de nada Pilar Ah vale a
see if they are real friends and leave the
a ver si son amigos de verdad y dejan el
subject okay okay okay okay okay well In short
tema vale vale vale vale bueno Total que
Joan Plana says that it's a lie that they haven't
Joan plana dice que es mentira que no lo
convicted him but then he publishes a
han condenado pero luego publica un
piece of the sentence
trozo de la sentencia
in which he
en el que
says that Joan can be
dice que a Joan se le puede
said to have bullied an
decir que le hizo bullying a un niño
autistic child you remember that he has Jado of
autista os acordáis que él se ha Jado de
saying that utbh can be called
decir que a utbh se le puede decir
violent with women Well the
violento con las mujeres Bueno pues el
supreme court according to this piece that
tribunal supremo según este trozo que
writes not to bully an
escribe no hacer bullying a un niño
autistic child if I'm not mistaken it's that I don't
autista si no me equivoco es que no me
remember it's that in the end he doesn't stop he doesn't
acuerdo es que al final él no para no
stop resurrecting things m in which he
para de resucitar cosas m en las que
looks bad okay or rather if I'm not mistaken
queda mal vale o sea si no me equivoco
well and here is Sara Reverte eh
bueno y aquí está Sara reverte eh
criticizing the country eh criticizing the country
criticando al país eh criticando al país
eh that this is [ __ ]  country that is
eh que esto es una [__] de país que es
a piece of [ __ ] Justice look how
una [__] de Justicia mira que son unos
ignorant the judges of this country are Okay
ignorantes los jueces de este país Vale
and what and you win or lose according to the
y que y que tú ganas o pierdes según la
lottery okay
lotería vale
look and here is their Twitter dedicated to
mira y aquí está su Twitter dedicado a
me Well today they have it today they have it
mí Bueno hoy la tienen hoy la tienen
eh today they have it set up
eh hoy la tienen montada
What do you want wizard today they have it
Con qué quieres wizard hoy la tienen
set up
montada
with I'm supposed to
con se supone que me tengo que
laugh this isn't supposed to be
reír se supone que esto no tiene que
funny wizard according to you
hacer gracia wizard según tú
no according to you no Well then nothing we
no según tú no Bueno pues nada nos
all split our sides laughing wiar Look we're
partimos todos de risa wiar Mira estamos
all here
aquí todos
cracking up and then it says something else
descojonando y luego dice otra
this Ruling says something else at the
cosa esta Providencia dice otra cosa al
end that there is no appeal against the present
final que es contra la presente
resolution Wait let's make
resolución no cabe recurso Espérate que
it bigger let's see if this is
lo ponemos más grande a ver si esto se
also seen against the present resolution there is
ve también contra la presente resolución
no
no cabe
appeal what does this mean
recurso qué quiere esto decir
you can go to the
que tú puedes ir al tribunal
Constitutional Court Of course you can
constitucional Por supuesto que puedes
go to the Constitutional Court and
ir al tribunal constitucional y con
later to the European Court of
posterioridad al tribunal europeo de
Human Rights Of course you can
Derechos Humanos Por supuesto que puede
go Even if you want you can file
ir Incluso si quieres puedes presentar
a complaint with the International Criminal Court
una denuncia en la Corte Penal
Of course you can
Internacional Por supuesto que puedes
file it and if you want you can go to Star
presentarla y si quieres te vas a a Star
Wars and file it in the courts of
Wars y lo presentas en los tribunales de
the galaxy you can do whatever you
la galaxia puedes hacer todo lo que tú
want but the sentence is final and it is
quieras pero la sentencia es firme y se
fulfilled period the sentence is final has
cumple punto la sentencia es firme has
lost nothing more Put yourself as you want put yourself
perdido nada más Ponte como quieras
as you want he lost
ponte como como te dé la gana ha perdido
because he insulted this man he dedicated himself
porque insultaba este señor se dedicaba
to insulting us Okay and to this one in particular
a insultarnos Vale y a este en concreto
Well there you have the gameover not to this
Bueno ahí tenéis el gameover no a este
partner in particular okay he told him He even told him
compañero en concreto vale le dijo Le
in a Apart from being in I
llegó a decir en un Aparte de estar en
don't know if in videos and live shows I don't
no sé si en vídeos y directos no me
remember where it was there were several
acuerdo dónde fue hubo varias cosas
strong things that he said about Adriá eh he started
fuertes que dijo de adriá eh se puso a
saying how I smelled stench in his house and we
decir como colí peste en su casa y
would have to open the windows because the
habría que abrir las ventanas porque el
guy smelled bad things like that okay in a tweet he even
tío olía mal cosas así vale en un twit
insulted him six times Tania
le llegó a poner seis insultos Tania
look look in the same t eh miserable
mira mira en el mismo t eh miserable
manipulator
manipulador
scavenger piece of [ __ ] and
carroñero trozo de [__] y
crazy Tania
pirado Tania
Sara
Sara
revert this how do you value it it
reverté esto como lo valoráis ustedes
violates the honor of
vulnera el honor de las
people How is this and they have condemned him
personas Cómo es esto y lo han condenado
in Costa because they have answered him they have
en Costa porque le han contestado le han
answered him they have put him in a
contestado le han puesto en
substitute it is that there is no more you have lost in the
sustito es que no hay más has perdido en
first instance you lost in the second
primera instancia has perdido en segunda
instance and you have lost in the supreme court that's it
instancia y has perdido en el supremo
assume it you have left A lot of money
ya está asúmelo te has dejado Una pasta
what you must have left
lo que se habrá dejado
man to make a fool of yourself I'm sorry it is
tío para hacer el ridículo lo siento es
like that I'm sorry there is no more  ok no more
así lo siento no hay más vale no hay más
Now if you want make a video saying
Ahora si quieres haces un vídeo diciendo
that the judge made up things that didn't
que el juez se ha inventado cosas que no
come out in the trial that I don't know what And
salieron en el juicio que no sé qué Y
that I don't know which my goodness okay
que no sé cuál madre mía vale
eh the courts of the galaxy volume
eh los tribunales de la galaxia volumen
3 with Cris prat indeed well
3 con Cris prat efectivamente bueno
now
ahora
now that I've been quiet I've been
ahora que yo me he estado calladito yo
quiet this whole
me he estado calladito toda esta
season
temporada
because Pablo now you tell me that if
porque Pablo ahora me dices eso de si
Pablo is the opposing lawyer it's
Pablo es el abogado contrario está
won
ganado
okay you're always with the same
vale que siempre estáis con la misma
bartender and I still haven't lost a [ __ ]
cantinera y yo sigo sin perder un [__]
trial And I've painted your face yeah
juicio Y a ti te he pintado la cara s ya
okay That's it relax
vale Ya está
calm down
relájate tranquilízate
says Carlos Olivarez 3000 per
dice Carlos olivarez a 3000 por
procedure plus the cost Carlos 3000 doesn't
procedimiento má la costa Carlos 3000 no
even cost him the first instance with
le cuesta ni la primera instancia con
those
esos
lawyers yes for me yes it cost me the
abogados si a m si a mí me costó la
first instance to defend myself
primera instancia defenderme
eh what about
eh lo de
Joan what about Joan I don't know if it was six or something like
Joan lo de Joan no sé si fu seis o por
that eh the first instance I don't know the
ahí eh la primera instancia no sé la
truth that costs a lot of money La
verdad eso cuesta mucho dinero la La
Movida Why do you think that opening the
Movida Por qué te crees que abrir la
box or rather the move eh is that
caja o sea la movida eh es que los
Joan Plana's lawyers are
abogados de Joan plana son los abogados
these lawyers from Jul  Janeiro and the I mean this one
estos de la jul Janeiro y la O sea este
has spent on each procedure and
se ha gastado en cada procedimiento y
then he has been resorting to the entire
aparte luego ha ido recurriendo a a toda
Supreme Court and everything no less than 15 has been
al supremo y todo no menos de 15 nos ha
spent on each
gastado por
procedure he has spent he has thrown
procedimiento se ha gastado ha tirado un
money away on burning he has thrown away
dinero en en arderse
money on burning man
ha tirado ha tirar dinero por ardor tío
how far can you go
hasta dónde puedes llegar
eh How far can you go eh Because it
eh Hasta dónde puedes llegar eh Porque
burns you that they leave you bad that it is an
te arda que te dejen mal que ya es un
issue that would not even be talked about trust you from 2020
tema que ni se hablaría fíate tú de 2020
until now
hasta hora
you know That's it don't do anymore the idiot
sabes Ya está no hagas más el idiota
vetega To the constitutional if you want that it seems to
vetee Al constitucional si quieres que a
me
mí me
Okay and to all these Tania you are going to
parece Vale y a todos estos Tania lo vas
read it in your in your channel you are going to leave
a leer en tu en tu canal lo vas a dejar
this sentence fixed on your channel like you
fijada esta sentencia en tu canal como
did with
hiciste con las de
Javi's I don't know anything no don't get up Don't
Javi No sé nada no no te levantes No te
get up in case your ankles
levantes vaya a ser que tus tobillos
suffer but whenever you want if you want
sufran pero cuando quieras si quieres la
put it
pones
come on Okay and to all these Tania you are going to
venga Vale y a todos estos Tania lo vas
read it in your today it is true Today was the
a leer en tu en tu hoy es verdad Hoy era
TR in the secret meeting it is true
lo de TR en la reunión secreta es verdad
But that is direct or it is a video or it is
Pero eso es directo o es un vídeo o es
a fake direct I will see it I will see tomorrow
un falso directo lo veo lo veo mañana ya
channel it  are you going to leave this
canal lo vas a dejar fijada esta
sentence fixed on your channel like you did with
sentencia en tu canal como hiciste con
Javi's Yeah yeah man, the
las de Javi Sí sí ya hombre que el
right to honor to me if they violate my
derecho al honor a mí que me vulneren el
honor my goodness nothing no don't get up
honor madre mía nada no no te levantes
eh don't get up in case your
eh no te levantes vaya a ser que tus
ankles suffer but whenever you want if you
tobillos sufran pero cuando quieras si
want you put it come on what a
quieres la pones venga
pap peada eh God
vaya pap peada eh Dio
this one here he himself explains his
este aquí él mismo te explica su
sentence here he tries to make you believe that
sentencia aquí intenta hacer creer que
I go around insulting people like this because I
yo voy insultando a la gente así por a
go crazy Calling people
lo loco que voy Llamando a la gente
insults like crazy he does this and
insultos a lo loco esto lo hace él y lo
this whole gang does it eh this rabble
hace toda esta pandilla eh esta gentuza
that tries to eliminate me by putting up out
que intentan eliminarme poniendo tweets
of context tweets without knowing
descontextualizados sin sin saber de
where they come from Look how he insults Look how he
dónde vienen Mira cóm insulta Mira cóm
insults I've already said that if they get involved with you you
insulta yo ya he dicho que si contigo Se
can answer but I'm not going that way well
meten tú puedes contestar pero yo no voy
that's what happened to you with
por ahí pues eso es lo que te pasó con
Adriá Okay So what's going on what
adriá Vale Total que qué es lo que pasa
happened today and that's why I'm
lo que ha pasado hoy y por eso os estoy
giving you a little context here okay I already
dando un poco de contexto aquí vale que
talked about this yesterday the salsería It's that
ya esto lo hablé ayer la salsería Es que
this man eh I, I haven't seen many
este hombre eh yo yo no he visto muchas
things from this man okay No no  I know
cosas de este hombre vale No no conozco
a lot of his content
mucho sus contenidos salseo
spicy sauce he was a follower of mine he was a fan of
picante él era seguidor mío él era fan
mine he he gave me the clicks on Twitter
mío él él me ponía en Twitter los click
like cats And that's not him he gave me
como las gatas Y eso no el él me ponía
the clicks on Twitter of Pepa of
los clicks en Twitter de la [__] de los
Pepa's live shows and such that
directos de la [__] y tal que
we react here not of the geeks and that's
reaccionamos aquí no de los friky y eso
worth suddenly one day I don't know what it was I
vale de repente un día no sé qué es lo
think it was that I sent him to
que fue creo que fue que lo mandé al
hell because he defended Peppa with
[__] porque defendió a la Peppa con lo
the
de los
240 but not to me where do they have to
240 pero no a m a donde tienen que de
where does he get the money from If you ruined
dónde saca el dinero Si tú le hundiste
his film career and his
su carrera cinematográfica y su canal de
YouTube channel woman with her hand on her forehead
YouTube mujer con la mano en la frente
woman with her hand on her forehead woman with her
mujer con la mano en la frente mujer con
hand on her forehead he charged many
la mano en la frente él cobraba muchos
millions for his films he sold them and
millones por sus películas las vendía y
on YouTube he was a successful YouTuber he
en YouTube era un exitoso youtuber
also puts it in the lawsuit eh this one
también lo pone en la demanda eh esta
that he has filed now to claim money
que ha puesto ahora para reclamar dinero
eh And because of me no longer because of me it's
eh Y por mi culpa ya no por mi culpa ya
no longer worth it I cut him off I cut his career
no vale le le corté le corté la carrera
the point is that eh well this man
la cuestión es que Eh bueno este hombre
was a fan he defended Peppa I think that was it he
era fan defendió a la Peppa creo que fue
defended Peppa it
eso que defendió a la Peppa se le
appeared to him one day  to Peppa in the chat and and
apareció un día a la Peppa en el chat y
and he defended her from the 240 thing and
y y la defendió de lo de los 240 y
then I told him go [ __ ]
entonces le dije vete a tomar por el
yourself something like that and because of that comment in
culo algo así y ya por ese comentario en
notes he started hanging out with them again he
notas se volvió a juntarse con ellos él
hung out with well him he even did
se juntaba con bueno él él incluso hizo
collaborations with Elena eh talking
colaboraciones con la Elena eh hablando
against the freaks I don't know I don't know
en contra de los friky no sé no sé
how much Well what always happens with
cuánto Bueno lo siempre lo que pasa con
these lotuses okay one thing the
los lotos estos vale que de una cosa al
next day the other okay I mean they
día siguiente los otro vale o sea te
try to get things out of you the good way
intentan sacar las cosas por las buenas
and if not the bad way Total that apparently
y si no por las malas Total que por lo
apparently
visto por lo visto
Hey wizard
Oye wizard
man wizard this thing about publishing my
tío wizard esto de que publiquen mis
conversations on WhatsApp in the
conversaciones en WhatsApp en el grupo
salseria Twitter group What
de la salseria de Twitter Qué
is it but come on but come on I mean I do
es pero vamos pero vamos o sea yo son
n't understand these are things wizard I mean I'm
cosas que no las entiendo wizard O sea
not answering you anymore not even to a [ __ ]
ya no te contesto más ni a un [__]
WhatsApp man new pinned post in la
WhatsApp tío nuevo post fijado en la
salseria la salseria is the group of the
salsería la salsería es el grupo de el
group not the WhatsApp one the one on
grupo no el de WhatsApp el de El de
Twitter okay here you go to my
Twitter vale aquí os vais al perfil mío
Twitter profile and here you have the community
de Twitter y aquí tenéis la comunidad
where the kids are the gentlemen Well
que está la chavalería la señoreros Pues
here the guy eh has appeared to very
aquí el colega eh le ha aparecido a bien
public  well first of all this is the name you have
public bueno lo primero este nombre es
given me on WhatsApp
el que me tienes puesto en el WhatsApp
this
este
[ __ ] and I sent him a
[__] y le he mandado antes un
WhatsApp before and he and the guy saw fit to
WhatsApp y el y el tío lo lo ha tenido a
publish it Well look because he felt like
bien publicarlo Pues mira porque le ha
it I'm warning you about what
[__] les estoy avisando de lo que me
you asked me no but let's see This is something
pediste no pero a ver Esto es una cosa
that I don't know if it is very very
que no sé yo si queda muy muy
professional for my
profesional para mis
followers I really can't
seguidores yo de verdad no no os puedo
answer you even on a WhatsApp man I can't
contestar ni a un WhatsApp tío que no
see how you get well In short this
vea cómo os ponéis bueno Total que este
man has started to comment on the
hombre se ha puesto a a comentar la
sentence to Joan
condena a Joan
Planas what what you should
planas lo que lo que tendrían que estar
all be doing
todos
no don't comment on the news Well
no no comentáis las noticias Pues bueno
this news this news is [ __ ]
esta noticia esta noticia es de [__]
great okay let's listen to a little what
madre vale vamos a escuchar un poco lo
he said Now now I will tell you
que él ha dicho Ahora ahora os diré el
why Joan Planas has
Por qué Joan planas ha perdido
definitively lost the trial we have to
definitivamente el juicio hay que
remember that joh en planas had
acordarnos que joh en planas había
sued the nicoteca he had sued
demandado la nicoteca había demandado a
Javi oliveira and had sued for
Javi oliveira y había demandado a
freedom and whatever comes up with the nicoteca he
libertad y lo que surja con la nicoteca
couldn't with Javi oliveira yes he could but
no pudo con Javi oliveira sí pudo pero
neither Well yes he
tampoco Bueno si
could 0 eur eh he could delete some
pudo 0 eur eh pudo borrar unos
videos he could with  freedom whatever arises or in other words
vídeos pudo con libertad lo que surja o
with freedom he couldn't handle the nicotine he
sea con libertad no pudo con la nicoteca
couldn't only with Javi if he could Javi didn't
no pudo solo con Javi si pudo Javi no
want to as if they didn't ask him for money well he didn't
quiso como como no le pedían dinero pues
want to now How do you
no quiso
say why am I going to appeal a
dice para qué voy a recurrir una una
sentence of 0
sentencia de 0
euros How do you say appeal appeal appeal
eur Cómo se dice apelar apelar apelar
and the thing is that here it is definitive
y la cosa está en que aquí es definitivo
because Joan Planas says has lost Yes that's what we're
porque dice Joan planas ha perdido Sí
going to see Leo
eso es lo que vamos a ver Leo
definitively the judge could
definitivamente el juiz pudo
partially it was a partial estimate
parcialmente fue una estimación parcial
Reyes but I'm telling you eh of 80,000 that he
Reyes pero ya te digo eh de 80.000 que
asked for and that he deleted all the videos to
pidió y de que borrara todos los vídeo a
what it was If it was worth it to him
a lo que fue Si a él le mereció la pena
Well it's not that it was worth it it's that
Bueno no es que le mereció la pena es
now he's spent another money on
que ahora se ha gastado otro dinero en
filing another lawsuit eh to claim that we
poner otra demanda eh para reclamar que
didn't give him money in the first one well
no le dimos dinero en la primera bueno
next year we'll fight it that's it he's
el año que viene lo pelearemos
taken me to the
io ya está me ha llevado al tribunal
supreme court but they've told her that
supremo pero la han dicho que a tomar
to hell now we can say that John Planas
por culo ya podemos decir que John plana
looks like
se parece a
Hitler appeal yes yes yes yes appeal Eh
Hitler recurrir sí sí sí sí recurrir Eh
well he won because the freedom lawyer
pues ganó porque el abogado de libertad
is Pablo Franco and he wins the case
lo jurja es Pablo Franco y gana el caso
against Joan Planas Joan Planas already  he started to
a Joan planas Joan planas ya se echó a
cry because there is nothing more to
llorar porque es que ya no hay más que
admit, in other words, he took it to the
admitir o sea lo llevó hasta el tribunal
Supreme Court, in other words, he loses the first one, come on, he appeals, he
supremo o sea él pierde el primero venga
loses again Joan Planas and
recurre vuelve a perder Joan planas y se
goes to
va hasta el
court, he loses according to Tania, he was going to
tribunal pierde según Tania la iba a
win eh Where is he going, where else does he have to
ganar eh A dónde va a dónde más tiene
appeal, the Galactic Court, the
que recurrir al tribunal galáctico al
Star
tribunal de Star
Wars Court, well, there is no more up, in other words, he can't do anything else
Wars tribunal pues ya ya no hay más para
so he
entonces pierde
definitely loses but That speaks to the
definitivamente pero Eso habla de la
obsession of this gentleman Joan Planas with
obsesión de este señor Joan planas por
wanting to be right Why does he lose the
querer tener la razón Por qué pierde el
first one, it's okay for him to appeal, come on, they
primero está bien que recurra venga le
kick him again in the second one
le meten otro otra patada en el segundo
Well, I'm going to go all the way to the Supreme Court
Pues voy a ir hasta el máximo tribunal
too, there is no more up where there is no
también ya no hay más para dónde ya no
more up now You already lost. Hey,
hay más para arriba ya Ya perdiste Oye
by the way, remember that we have a
por cierto recordaros que tenemos un
goal today of 50, okay, it's 7 out of 50, I don't
objetivo hoy de 50 vale van 7 de 50 no
know what I put in the text but it's a
sé lo que he puesto de texto pero es un
joke for all these people, okay, so they
sasca para toda esta gente vale para que
criticize me tomorrow also for
me critiquen mañana también por
monetizing and he has to pay costs and he
monetizar y tiene que pagar costas y
has to pay costs, no, YouTube, that's the
tiene que pagar costas no youtub así se
name of the channel Libertad de los Gesur and there is
llama el canal libertad de los gesur y
no more  up, I mean, okay
ya no hay más para arriba o sea vale
orus, thank you very much,
orus muchas gracias muchas
thank you very much, there's no more you can't
gracias ya no hay más ya no puedes
appeal anymore, you've already spent your three
recurrir más ya ya gastaste tus tres
chances. Well, whatever
oportunidades Pues que tenga los
followers you have, if you know, slow, well, do
seguidores que tenga si sabes lentita
n't count on me, who's
pues no cuentes conmigo a quien le habla
Victoria talking to? eh, another stubborn one, yes, another stubborn one, it's
Victoria eh otro terco sí otro terco es
that he went all the way against libert
que se fue hasta el último contra libert
J. surge, he had sued a a jav,
J surja él había demandado a a a jav
okay, the half that now he starts to go over
vale la midad que ahora se pone a
this a little, I've been seeing it,
repasar un poco esto lo estado viendo yo
okay, he starts to read the sentence, the
vale se pone a leer la sentencia el
ruling, okay,
fallo vale
and we're talking about the supreme court,
e estamos hablando del tribunal supremo
okay, he starts to read the rulings and over
vale se pone a leer los fallos y por
here he's seeing that he starts to go over
aquí está viendo que se pone a repasar
something a little, not from the past, well, no. I mean, not even,
poco algo no del pasado bueno no O sea
eh, not even. It's just there. This is
eh Ni siquiera Solamente ya está Esto es
what he comments on, eh, I mean, the client
lo que Comenta eh o sea pone el cliente
that we saw before also puts it here. Well,
que hemos visto antes también aquí Bueno
look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look,
mira Mirad Mirad mir mir mir mir mir
if she's here, look at her, look at her, you
Mirad si está aquí Mírala
see her here, a lie, says Sara
mírala la veis aquí mentira dice Sara
Ryar, that's a
ryar que es
lie, okay, that's a lie,
mentira
okay. And then what they're
mentira okay Y entonces lo que están
doing is putting it green, what's the
haciendo es ponerlo verde si de qué
use of ra, wait, what they're doing is
sirve ra espera lo que están haciendo es
put it green because you can't say that
ponerlo verde porque no puedes decir eso
Look, look here she has it, sar rar in the
Mira mira aquí la tiene la sar rar en el
chat Troy is burning now we're going to see what
chat arde Troya que ahora vamos a ver lo
Troy is commenting on about
que está comentando arde Troya sobre
this sentence that you're going to love Okay
esta sentencia que os va a encantar Vale
and and
y y
puts spicy sauce after the live stream
pone salseo picante después del directo
that you did defaming and repeating
que has hecho difamando y repitiendo las
Javi's lies you should better
mentiras de Javi mejor deberías de
shut up because you're a defamer like
callarte que eres un difamador como
them, I mean, she revives them eh
ellos o sea las revive eh las revive
this girl revives them eh you defend a Chavista and
esta chica eh defiendes a un chavista y
the dictatorship of Venezuela and you have
a la dictadura de Venezuela y has
defamed and lied now she's a Chavista
difamado y mentido ahora es chavista
like Calo Salgado
como el calo Salgado
eh my goodness my goodness my goodness she's
eh madre mía madre mía madre mía lo está
putting it green look at your ideology is being a
poniendo verde mira tu ideología es ser
repeater of Javi's defamations
repetidor de las difamaciones de
man that's how they are
Javi tío así
the moment they have left the
son en el momento que se han salido del
or look at what the man has said, I mean,
o se fíjate tú lo que ha dicho el hombre
what he has said is eh what he
o sea que lo que ha dicho es eh lo que
has said is what it is, they have condemned him
ha dicho es lo que es lo han condenado
without further ado, he has lost I was putting up a
sin más ha perdido Estaba poniendo una
silly
tontería de
lawsuit says Magi But Javi for the
demanda dice Magi Pero Javi para las
people who are in a
personas que estamos en un momento
delicate moment Could you put one so that each one can
delicado Podrías poner un que cada uno
do the super chat  that I can Ah well
haga el super chat que pueda Ah bueno
but Magi the people who are in a
pero Magi las personas que estén en un
delicate moment should not do any
momento delicado que no hagan ningún
super chat no whoever can not do
super chat no el que pueda que no hagan
any, as long as you are here give
ninguno yo con que estéis aquí deis
likes and all that stuff to me, it's
likes y todas esas cosas a mí me a mí me
good for me, it serves me okay or so super
viene bien me sirve vale o sea super
chat and member And that whoever can do it
chat y miembro Y eso que lo hagas quien
okay here you can enjoy the
pueda vale aquí se puede disfrutar del
content and we have a laugh okay super
contenido y echamos una risa vale super
chat is extra
chat es extra
the Team of the bad ones are going to have a
al Team de los malitos les va a dar un
colic with the week they have had face
cólico con la semanita que llevan cara
crying with laughter face crying with laughter
llorando de risa cara llorando de risa
face crying with laughter and when they win one it's
cara llorando de risa y cuando ganan una
not of much use either because of course
no sirve tampoco de mucho porque claro
the expectations they have
es que ellos las expectativas que tienen
with winning or losing you
con ganar o perder
are a fanatic who monetizes by
la eres un fanático que monetizas
defaming Ah okay okay okay okay that of
difamando Ah vale vale vale vale que
course It's that I the expectation they
claro Es que yo la expectativa que
have with winning or losing the sentences
tienen con ganar o perder las sentencias
are that they are right in the debate in
son que les da la razón en el debate en
the in the history that they have The Movida
la en la historia que tengan La Movida
that they have you know but no no that's not okay
que tengan sabes pero no no es eso vale
But well we already have ard de Troya which
Pero bueno ya tenemos ard de Troya que
is the one who defends the sentence as it
es el que defiende la sentencia según le
suits him yes yes what's the use what's the use
convenga si si de qué sirve de qué sirve
if the lawyer does not do it well that
si el abogado no lo hace bien que lo
who can do it better than a
quién lo puede hacer mejor que un
lawyer  if he himself has skipped that
abogado si él mismo se ha saltar ese
step he hasn't realized that And he is
paso no se ha da cuenta de eso Y está
so proud saying in the last part
tan ufano diciendo en la última parte
see It's that look look it's your turn to
ver Es que mira mira que te le toca
pay costs but I'm not going to see if it
pagar costas pero es que no voy a ver si
looks good to look look who has to
se ve bien a mira mira que tiene que
pay costs let's see that you are the one who
pagar costas a ver que eres tú el que
studies law I don't study anything we already
estudia leyes yo no estudia nada ya lo
suspected it to de Troya Well that's
sospechábamos a de Troya Pues eso por
for money man well that's it well if there
por dinero hombre pues ya está pues si
are
son
6445 visits Aha well the fact is that
6445 visitas Ajá bueno el hecho es que
Joan Planas lost aha No no Ah that he didn't
Joan planas perdió ajá No no Ah que no
lose what diar de Troya that he didn't
perdió que diar de Troya que no
lose no he didn't lose just like
perdió no no perdió igual que el marido
Tania's husband didn't
de Tania tampoco
lose Good night Javi
perdió Buenas noches Javi
handsome with your crazy uncombed hair it
guapo con el pelo alocado sin peinar te
gives you youth I wanted to say it well well
da juventud quería decirlo bueno bueno
but but well every day we can
pero pero bueno cada día podemos
comb our hair in a certain way that's what
peinarnos de una manera es lo que tiene
hair has it's what it has have hair that's what it has having
el pelo es lo que tiene ten el pelo es
hair that every day you
lo que tiene tener el pelo que cada día
can comb it in a certain way not like
te puedes peinar de una forma no como al
de Troya who has the
de Troya que todos los días tiene el
same
mismo
look every day Hey let's see listen to me Joan Plana
look Oye a ver escúchame Joan plana
loses first instance second
pierde primera instancia segunda
instance provincial hearing and
instancia audiencia provincial y
supreme court sentences in  Costa has
tribunal supremo condena en Costa ha
lost to
perdido a de
Troy no no What's up What's up what's up I've
Troya no no Qué va Qué Va qué va Yo he
seen Loli's staples I've seen
visto las grapas de Loli yo he visto las
Loli's staples No he hasn't lost he hasn't lost It's just
Loli No no ha perdido no ha perdido Solo
that he didn't win right Nica Of course well that's it he has
que no ganó verdad Nica Claro pues ya
n't
está no ha
[Laughs]
[Risas]
won can you give me this click with
ganado me podéis [__] este click con
quality please but this is fantasy
calidad por favor pero esto que fantasía
[Laughs]
[Risas]
eh Jordi what do those of Troy say that
eh Jordi que dice las de Troya que
Johannas hasn't
johanas no ha
lost that she hasn't won She simply hasn't
perdido que no ha ganado Simplemente no
won hey hey hey hey hey
ganado oye oye oye oye
the derby the derby Sevilla betti is worth
oye el derbi el derbi Sevilla betti vale
the derby Sevilla betti
el derbi Sevilla betti
eh five goals for Sevilla zero for Beti
eh cinco goles del Sevilla cero del beti
has lost Beti no It simply didn't
ha perdido el beti no Simplemente no
win like this it's like a tie Ah It's
ganó como esto es como un empate Ah Es
like a tie it's like a tie But
como un empate es como un empate Pero
Javi Oliveira who was condemned to 0 euros that one that one
Javi oliveira que lo condenaron a 0 eur
is a defeat that one He's leaving he's leaving he's leaving the
ese ese es una derrota ese Se va se va
internet that one is leaving the
se va se va de internet ese se va de
internet man but it's that they are like that and then they get
internet tío pero es que son así y luego
frustrated that we make fun of it
se frustran de que nos burlemos de ello
man I mean they are like that and and they wonder
tío o sea son así y y se preguntan por
why we make fun of them why they don't
qué nos cachondeos de ellos por qué no
grow  Why are people not with
crecen Por qué la gente no está con
them, good people,
ellos la gente de
tie, tie, yes, yes, yes, a tie that
empate empate sí sí sí sí un empate que
the boy has got, come on, a tie,
le ha salido al muchacho vamos un empate
come on, it's tremendous, eh, it's tremendous, I mean,
vamos es que es tremendo eh es tremendo
the other day Yan Plana was saying that
o sea el otro día yan plana diciendo que
he won, he beat me, but by a big margin, eh,
él ganó a mí me ganó pero muy ganado eh
Very whole, okay, but here, no, no,
Muy entero vale pero pero aquí no no
this is more or less a tie, they have
esto es más o menos un empate lo han
sentenced Joan to pay the costs, but but it
condenado a Joan a las costas pero pero
's a tie, of course, of course, Yes, yes, 00
es un empate Claro claro claro Sí sí 00
0, technical tie 33 33 Ah, okay, 33 33 33
0 empate técnico 33 33 Ah vale 33 33 33
that he has lost. The plan is not the first
que ha perdido El plan no primera
instance, the provincial court and the
instancia audiencia provincial y
supreme court, and now wherever he goes, well, he's
tribunal supremo y ahora donde Vaya pues
going to lose it too, it
también lo va a perder
seems that you have filed many
se ve que has Interpuesto muchos
appeals, I have none,
recursos de casación yo ninguno madre
my goodness, but in an appeal,
mía pero en un recurso pueden recurrir
both parties can appeal, as far as I understand, eh,
las dos partes que yo tenga entendido eh
Ah, okay, okay,
Ah vale vale vale pueden recurrir las
both parties can appeal because they don't agree,
dos partes porque no están de acuerdo
okay, okay, but it clearly tells me
vale vale vale Pero a me lo dice
in that one that if, if the
claramente en el ese que si si la otra
other party doesn't appeal, they don't have to pay the
la otra parte no recurre no tiene gasto
lawyer's fees, nor do they have to pay any expenses. No, there are no costs.
de abogado ni tiene gasto de nada No no
Ah, okay, okay, okay, after the
hay Costa Ah vale vale vale después del
live broadcast,
directo que
V goes, well  So then I don't have any
va V pues entonces pues entonces yo
expenses either, eh none, eh
tampoco tengo tengo gastos eh ninguno eh
almost, none of the procedures, I
casi Ninguno de los procedimientos me
piss myself on them all, says Maria, they're
meo todas dice María es que son
pathetic, man, I mean, who the [ __ ] watches these
patéticos tío o sea quién [__] ve estos
channels, man, let it not be here to
canales tío que que no sean aquí para
laugh, loving
reírnos
lies, better
amando mentira mejor
than who the [ __ ] watches this loser, I mean, let it not
que quién [__] vea este pringado o sea
be for an anno joke, no
que no sea para cachón de anno no